What more is there to say, really?
더 할 말이 뭐가 있겠어요?
Tomorrow is the day for results.
내일이면 결과가 나오겠죠
A day that very excited indeed about.
정말 흥분되는 날이었죠
Uh.
네
But I will mention everything that you can do at this point generating text and code with frontier models
이 시점에서 할 수 있는 모든 걸 말씀드리죠 프론티어 모델과 API로 텍스트와 코드를
and their APIs, open source models through hugging faces, various libraries, tools, assistance,
생성하고 얼굴을 끌어안기, 다양한 라이브러리 도구, 지원, 래그 모델을 통해서요
It's all part of your skill set.
다 실력의 일부예요
You can follow the five step strategy I went through to solve problems including curating data, building
제가 다뤘던 5단계 전략을 따르시면 됩니다 큐레이팅 데이터 문제 해결과 기본
a baseline model, and fine tuning frontier model with example training sets in those jsonl the JSON
모델 구축 개척자 모델을 미세 조정하는 거죠 업로드한 jsonl의 JSON
lines files that we uploaded, and now and now you can run Q Laura fine tuning for open source models,
라인 파일에 대한 훈련 세트와 함께요 Q 로라 미세 조정도 실행할 수 있습니다 hyperpaameter를
including defining and selecting your hyperparameters.
정의 및 선택하는 것도 포함해서요
And then you can run training and you can monitor training.
훈련도 실행하고 모니터링도 할 수 있죠
And a great joy it is to uh, so tomorrow, you will be able to run inference on a fine tuned model,
내일 여러분은 미세 튜닝 모델에 대한 추론을 실행할 수 있을 겁니다 생각만큼 간단하지
which isn't as simple as it sounds, because you can't just load it in.
않아요 그냥 로드할 수 없으니까요
You have to know how to load in the base model and apply these chullora weights on top of it.
베이스 모델을 로드하고 출로라 추를 그 위에 붙이는 법을 알아야 해요
But it's not that difficult.
그렇게 어렵진 않아요
But but it is.
하지만 사실이에요
There are a couple of steps to it.
몇 가지 단계가 있어요
Uh, and then, of course, we'll take a moment to look at the results.
그 후에 결과를 보도록 하죠
Um, but most importantly, at that point, you will be able to carry out the end to end process from
하지만 가장 중요한 것은 그 시점에서 상업적 문제의 아이디어와 사고, 정의를
first idea and thought and definition of the commercial problem through to having a trained model,
종단 간 프로세스로 수행할 수 있다는 것입니다 훈련된 모델을 통해
uh, to build your own proprietary verticalized LLM to solve a business problem.
독자적인 수직화 LLM을 구축해 사업적 문제를 해결할 수 있죠
And I was going to try and put a third bullet in there, because I've normally had three bullets against
세 번째 총알을 넣으려고 했어요 내일 할 작업에서는 보통 세 발을
the what you'll be able to do tomorrow.
넣거든요 Put
But it seems to me like that second bullet is enough of a mic drop that it's like you don't need a third
하지만 두 번째 총알로 충분히 유명해져서 세 번째 총알은 필요 없는 것 같아요
bullet.
그거면 돼요
That second bullet, it says it all.
두 번째 총알이 모든 걸 말해 줘요
That's what you're going to be able to do.
그게 여러분이 할 수 있는 거죠
And it's huge.
정말 커요
I'll see you then.
그때 봐요